softwarediscountcodes.com 2009-06-19

# Privacy Policy - Software Discount Codes

Back to the Software Discount Codes Store

**Software Discount Codes Privacy Policy**

In relation to the website: www.softwarediscountcodes.com ("the Site").  
Run By: DML ("we/us").

The Site is a UK based website and complies with the requirements of the UK Data Protection Act 1998 relating to the personal information you supply on the Site. The Site uses a security system that protects your information from unauthorised use. However, as no data transmissions over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk.

What information we hold about you

Software Discount Codes do not hold any information about you when you purchase a product. All information will be held by the Software Retailer so we would ask that you refer to the relevant publisher's Privacy Policy before you purchase a product from them. You may optionally decide to opt in to receive our newsletter and special offers. In this case we would store your email address, name and any other details you may submit securely. You may opt-out of this at any time by using the unsubscribe information at the bottom of each email. We will never sell, trade or show your email address and contact details to other parties.   
Cookies

In addition to the information which you supply to us, information and data may be automatically collected through the use of cookies. Cookies are small text files the Site can use to recognise repeat users and allow us to observe behaviour and compile aggregate data in order to improve the Site for you. Cookies also allow us to count the number of unique and return visitors to our Site.  
Some of our associated companies may themselves use cookies on their own websites. We have no access to, or control of these cookies, should this occur. You can easily remove cookies from your machine, should you wish to do so, by deleting them from your browser. Unfortunately, we cannot accept liability for any malfunctioning of your PC or its installed web browser as a result of your seeking to follow these instructions.  
We may monitor customer traffic patterns, Site usage and related Site information in order to optimise your use of the Site and we may give aggregated statistics to a reputable third-party, but these statistics will include no information personally identifying you.   
Your Consent

By using our web site you consent to us using the personal information you have given us and our trusted partners, as outlined in this Privacy Policy.  
Please note that we do provide links to other sites, which may not be governed by this Privacy Policy and you should view the particular privacy policies of those sites for further information.  
We may occasionally modify this Privacy Statement, such variations becoming effective immediately upon posting to the Site and by continuing to use the Site, you will be deemed to accept any such variations. 

Back to the Software Discount Codes Store

### Free Software!

Sign up to our free   
**email newsletter**   
and win prizes every month!!

### Our Top Software Picks
